[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
All right, I'm listening.
Here's what I noticed.
The way he moves isn't ordinary.
Like Chiara's.
Better dig deeper, Agent Dara.
But did you know Viktor was transferred to another prison?
When did that happen?
They didn't report it to me.
I only found out just now.
But it looks like they transferred him the other night.
To the most secluded area,
and Viktor was transferred to maximum security.
You criminals sure do talk a lot.
Boss, just relax.
This guy from Prague looks tough, huh?
All right, then.
Let's teach him a lesson.
Boss, that's enough.
You don't have to do this anymore.
I'll take it all!
I don't think I've seen her around here before.
Maybe she's attending the wedding.
Huh?!
We only invited a few people.
Maybe she's from Chiara's side.
And you know Chiara and I only wanted our closest friends and family
to be invited to the wedding.
Mom?
We were just talking about how he misses his mom.
And now they finally meet!
That's so nice for Rahmboy!
Mama Yaya?
Mom!
I've missed you.
That's Rahmboy's mother!
Rahmboy?
I've missed you so much.
Look how big you've gotten!
You used to be a baby crying to Mom because you had poop in your butt.
Look at you now!
You're even taller than me, aren't you, son?
Mom.
Mom, you're embarrassing me in front of Aunt Tess and Uncle Mario.
Come on, Rahmboy. It's okay! Your mom is really funny.
By the way, I'm Tess!
Tess.
I'm Mario.
Mario and Tess.
Mari-Tess?
What a perfect match!
Like a love team, just like QuenDrea.
Vicky, you're really keeping up with everything.
Of course! I have a Gen-Z kid.
So I'm always updated on the latest trends.
Right! Like mother, like son.
Oh, Vicky, did you know? Rahmboy livestreams all day.
Mama Yaya.
My dear.
Mama Yaya?
What do you mean? Are you and Chiara siblings?
No, we're not. I don't get it either.
Mama Yaya raised and took care of me when I was a child.
She's always there when I trained in Sicily.
The only one who's very special to me.
-Hello. -Hello, ma'am.
Well, Vicky, it's a double celebration after all!
Exactly! Isn't it amazing?
Of all places, you happened to reunite with Aunt Vicky here in Albay.
You can just call me Mom Vicky.
Ah yes! Mom Vicky, I'm Mikoy.
-Mikoy. -That's right.
I'm Chiara's fiancé.
Oh, really? You're getting married, dear?
Yes! To my greatest love.
Looks like I came at just the right time.
With all due respect, Mom Vicky.
How long will your vacation in the Philippines be?
I'm never going back abroad.
I've been a domestic helper there for so long,
taking care of someone else's child.
Now it's time for me to take care of my own child.
Right, son?
There you go! You really are the best mom!
That's really great to hear!
You deserve your early retirement, Mama Yaya.
You've sacrificed so much all these years.
I really hope you can make it to my wedding.
Are you sure, dear?
Is that okay with you, Mikoy?
Who am I to say no to my sweetheart's Mama Yaya?
Of course! You're more than welcome, Mom Vicky.
Thank you.
What a wonderful day this is!
Vicky, I've got some kakanin and calamansi juice for you, too!
-Right timing! -Go on.
Perfect timing. There's biko!
-You all are so good at that. -How did you find out?
-How did you know? -That's what you're good at!
You're still a child back then.
Come on, Vicky, let's have a snack.
Of course, Mom.
Aunt Vicky, have some biko!
I was assigned to La Morte Bianca's villa before.
As a domestic worker.
I didn't even know who they were.
Until I found out I was working for the mafia.
See? In-law was right all along.
That La Morte Bianca is shameless.
You know, heaven or hell, wherever she is now, I hope she stays there for good!
That explains why you're the one who raised Chiara.
I raised Donatello too.
If only I could've kept them away back then, I would have.
You want more, sweetheart?
This is so good.
This is so good. It really is, Mom!
Go ahead, eat up!
All right.
Maybe you want more. You can take mine.
Really? Sure!
Just a little more.
I'ts okay to cry.
It won't make you weak.
Here, have something to eat. Go on!
You'll be training again later.
Eat up!
Here's yours.
Thank you.
Are you okay, Mom Vicky?
Of course, Mikoy!
I'm just so happy to be with my child,
and also this girl I raised as my own.
It's a small world after all.
You guys take care of our guests.
Perfect!
Are you Viktor?
Relax, boss!
Senator wants us to welcome you.
Chill out, boss!
Sir Vik!
Easy, boss!
Mr. Viktor!
Give us a smile!
Okay, one more!
Let's go. Just leave him.
Sir Vik!
Are you okay, boss?
I'm staying right here.
Could Senator Quentin finally be getting back at Viktor?
Now's finally his chance!
Ever since the Moravianos arrived in the Philippines,
the Sinigang Cartel's operations have come to a halt!
His side hustle got shut down, so now he's getting revenge!
And he can get back at him by making Viktor's life miserable
while his case is in court.
But wouldn't going after Viktor put Senator Quintin's ties
to the Sinigang Cartel at risk?
Unless he has other plans for Viktor.
Just like us, we're keeping him because he has valuable information for us.
You mean, Senator Quintin needs something from Viktor?
What could it be?
Referrals to criminals in Europe?
Business contacts?
For a businessman posing as a public servant?
What you are saying is not impossible.
Sen. Look at this.
YESTERDAY
You know what?
If this is effective for Chiara, well and good!
And if not,
well, we still have Donabel.
Oh, that's panful!
Especially that one.
You know what?
I can't remember any stories from Chiara about her Mama Yaya.
Really?
Maybe because Chiara was still young back then.
She can't remember anything. Right?
That's true.
Or it also can be
after all that Chiara went through as a child,
she doesn't want to revisit those memories anymore.
Can be.
If you think about it,
since she was a child, La Morte Bianca has been training her
to fight and hold a gun.
Too much, right? Her childhood is so traumatic.
Let's just think about this.
Look at Chiara now. She's so happy.
That's right, Dad.
After everything we've been through,
I've never seen her this happy before.
And because of that,
we need to celebrate with a delicious dinner!
-Yes! -Yes!
Okay, okay! I'll head to the market while it's still light,
and I'll pick up something to grill.
-Ooh! -Wait, wait!
Honey, could you buy me lots of tomatoes?
-I'm making a salad. -Okay!
Uncle Mario, get me some hotdogs too. For the kolokoys.
All right, sure!
Hey! Easy on the biko!
Why?
I missed this!
Can you not? Mind your own snack!
Wait, wait. Captain Pepe,
you've been so quiet.
He ate a lot too!
He probably hasn't digested it yet, huh?
It's not like that.
Then what?
It's just that Aunt Vicky isn't from around here.
Why did she suddenly show up?
Of course, she just got here.
Yes, and Chiara knows her.
She seems nice.
And trustworthy too.
I hope so. I hope you're right.
This is unbelievable, Mama Yaya.
I can't believe we're seeing each other again!
What a coincidence, right?
This is no coincidence, dear.
None of this is a coincidence.
Didn't I tell you before?
There's something destined for each of us.
It's time, Chiara.
It's time for you to lead the Concordat.
Whatever you have here,
you need to leave it all behind.
As soon as possible.
Bro.
I just hope that after you and Sis Chiara get married,
I hope nothing changes.
What's going to change?
I don't know.
It's just…
You know how it is.
You and Sis Chiara might get busy.
And…
Well, you might not have time for me anymore.
We won't be able to hang out anymore.
We won't be able to vlog together.
Or go fishing here by the river.
Listen, Rahmboy.
Even after Chiara and I get married,
I'll still be your brother, okay?
And you, you'll still be a pain in my ass!
Geez. You're something else, Bro.
But okay.
You're right.
-You're right, anyway. -Nah, I'm just kidding!
Of course, nothing will change!
You know that, my Rahmboy! Oh, you.
Now, enough being dramatic, okay?
-I'm not! -Will you?
I'm not being dramatic.
-Yes, you are! -This is nothing!
I'm just making sure.
How do you do this again?
Oh, Bro!
Let's vlog first. This might be our last one.
There you go again with the drama.
What was that?
-Huh? -There's someone back there.
-Where? -They're wearing black!
-Huh?! -There they are!
-Bro! Bro! Wait! -Just come with us, bro!
-Do not resist. -Bro!
Quit fighting!
What's happening?
Help me!
Chiara!
Mom! Dad!
Okay, okay, okay!
Get in!
Chiara!
All right! Sounds like a success!
Enjoy, Bro Mikoy!
Really?
Kidnapping again?
Prague already traumatized me!
Hey!
Let me go!
Help! Hey!
Where are the girls?
I told you they're not answering!
Even the singers aren't picking up.
They ghosted us. Angelito!
Call this number, will you?
Angelito?
Oh, Bro, just keep quiet for a minute.
Hey!
I said quiet!
Even the dancers and the girls I contacted have canceled.
Because we haven't paid the down payment yet!
We're only just starting to pool our money.
Just put it on my tab for now, okay?
See? That's what I'm talking about.
Borrowing money again!
Hold still! It's not even yet. Wait!
Do I really need this?
You know, Sis Chiara, you're so beautiful!
Bro Mikoy is so lucky to have you.
But I'm just as lucky to have him and all of you.
Especially to the best maid of honor ever!
Here!
Let's solve this problem of yours.
Solve our problem?
Yes!
You haven't even contributed!
Exactly! You haven't even chipped in!
This is my contribution! I'm making the calls!
-Okay, then. -Cocoy!
You've been drinking this whole time, and you haven't contributed anything too!
Right!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! -Okay, okay, we're good!
We will behave, we promise!
It's okay now.
Don't mess with Cocoy! Those muscles will be the death of you.
We're screwed.
Wait, I think that's them!
-l'll get it. -No, I'll get it! I'll get it!
Give me that chair. Chiara, come sit here for a bit!
What's happening?
Let's hide.
What is that?
Here it is!
Wow!
Hello, in-law!
In-law.
Is Chiara there?
Aw, too bad she's not here.
Come on! It's her bridal shower.
Wait a minute. Do you need anything from her?
Or is something wrong?
Is something bothering you?
Nothing! I just wanted to check in on her.
Oh, she's definitely happy!
She's so excited for her wedding.
That's good to hear! Right?
I'm happy that our children is happy!
Oh.
Ah, okay, in-law! Thank you so much!
Take care over there. Good night!
Oh, hey! You take care, too. Wait, I have something--
Hello?
In-law?
They've stolen so many years from you, my child.
I won't do away with your happiness for now.
You deserve to be happy, Chiara. My daughter.
Viktor,
wherever you are,
promise me you'll come back.
There's something destined for each of us.
It's time for you to lead the Concordat.
Why did you really come back, Mama Yaya?
You know why I came back.
Let's see who you're hiding, Sean.
The world really is a small place, huh?
Who would've thought your Mama Yaya would turn out to be Rahmboy's mother?
Even I was surprised.
How come you never told me about your Mama Yaya?
To be honest, I just never thought we'd see each other again.
I'm glad you found each other again.
Right?
Let me go,
so we can talk normally, Carlota. Please.